Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - Job 296, Frankfort, 1 of 2,1958 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Job 296, Frankfort, 2 of 2,1958 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Job 296, Frankfort, Drawings,1958 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Job 297, Bay City,1958 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, 1 of 6,1959-1960 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, 2 of 6,1959-1960 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, 3 of 6,1959-1960 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, 4 of 6,1959-1960 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, 5 of 6,1959-1960 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, 6 of 6,1959-1960 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, Blueprints,1958 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 4,1959 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 4,1959 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 3 of 4,1959 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Job 298, City of Michigan, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 4 of 4,1959 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Job 299, St. Ignace and Mackinac Island,1958 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Job 300, Mackinaw Island,1958 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Job 301, Frankfort,1959 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Job 302, Kenosha, WI,1959 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Job 303, Kewaunee, WI, 1 of 2,1960 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Job 303, Kewaunee, WI, 2 of 2,1960 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Job 303, Kewaunee, WI, Drawings,1960 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Job 304, Jones Island, WI,1959 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Job 305, Frankfort,1960 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Job 306, Frankfort,1960 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Job 306, Frankfort, Drawings,1960 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, 1 of 3,1960 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, 2 of 3,1960 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, 3 of 3,1960 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 5,1960 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 5,1960 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 3 of 5,1960 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 4 of 5,1960 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 5 of 5,1960 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Formal Documents,1960 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Miscellaneous Drawings,1960 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Job 307, Burn’s Ditch, IN, Soundings, Related Work,1960 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Job 308, Ludington, 1 of 3,1960 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Job 308, Ludington, 2 of 3,1960 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Job 308, Ludington, 3 of 3,1960 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Job 308, Ludington, Drawings,1960 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Job 309, Kenosha, WI,1960 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Job 310, Frankfort,1960 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Job 311, St. Joseph, 1 of 3,1960 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Job 311, St. Joseph, 2 of 3,1960 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Job 311, St. Joseph, 3 of 3,1960 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Job 311, St. Joseph, Drawings,1960 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Job 312, Charlevoix,1960 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Job 312, Charlevoix, Blue – line Drawings,1960 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Job 313, Muskegon,1960 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Job 314, Manistique,1960 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Job 315, Charlevoix, 1 of 3,1961 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Job 315, Charlevoix, 2 of 3,1961 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Job 315, Charlevoix, 3 of 3,1961 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Job 315, Charlevoix, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1961 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Job 315, Charlevoix, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1961 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Job 316, St. Joseph, 1 of 2,1961-1962 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Job 316, St. Joseph, 2 of 2,1961-1962 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Job 316A, St. Joseph,1962 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Job 316A, St. Joseph, Drawings,1962 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, 1 of 4,1962 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, 2 of 4,1962 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, 3 of 4,1962 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, 4 of 4,1962 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 2,1962 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 2,1962 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, Blueprints,1962 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Job 317, Ogden Dunes, IN, Drawings,1962 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Job 318, West Olive,1962 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Job 318, West Olive, Drawings,1962 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Job 319, Muskegon, 1 of 3,1963 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Job 319, Muskegon, 2 of 3,1963 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Job 319, Muskegon, 3 of 3,1963 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Job 319, Muskegon, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 3,1963 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Job 319, Muskegon, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 3,1963 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Job 319, Muskegon, Blue – line Drawings, 3 of 3,1963 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Job 320, Racine, WI,1963 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Job 320, Racine, WI, Blue – line Drawings,1963 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Job 321, Racine, WI,1963 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Job 321, Racine, WI, Blue – line Drawings,1963 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Job 322, Kenosha, WI, 1 of 3,1963 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Job 322, Kenosha, WI, 2 of 3,1963 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Job 322, Kenosha, WI, 3 of 3,1963 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Job 322, Kenosha, WI, Drawings,1963 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Job 323, Elberta,1963 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Job 324, Frankfort,1963 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Job 325, Manistee,1963 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Job 326, Sheboygan, WI, 1 of 3,1963 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Job 326, Sheboygan, WI, 2 of 3,1963 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Job 326, Sheboygan, WI, 3 of 3,1963 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Job 326, Sheboygan, WI, Drawings,1963 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Job 327, Frankfort,1963 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Job 328, Frankfort,1963 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Job 329, Frankfort,1963 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Job 330, Frankfort,1964 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Job 331, Frankfort,1964 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Job 332, Frankfort,1964 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Job 333, Frankfort,1964 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Job 334, Mackinac Island, 1 of 4,1964 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Job 334, Mackinac Island, 2 of 4,1964 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Job 334, Mackinac Island, 3 of 4,1964 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Job 334, Mackinac Island, 4 of 4,1964 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Job 334, Mackinac Island, Drawings, 1 of 2,1964 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Job 334, Mackinac Island, Drawings, 2 of 2,1964 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Job 335, Frankfort,1964 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Job 336, Manistee,1964 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Job 337, Wyoming,1965 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Job 337, Wyoming, Black and Veatch Correspondence,1964-1966 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Job 337, Wyoming, Blue – line Drawings,1965 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Job 337, Wyoming, City of Wyoming Correspondence,1964-1967 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Job 337, Wyoming, Estimate, Contract and Bids,1964 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Job 337, Wyoming, Lamar Pipe Correspondence,1964-1965 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Job 337, Wyoming, O’Laughlin Construction Correspondence,1965 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Job 337, Wyoming, Receipt and Progress Schedule,1965 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Job 338, Frankfort,1964 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Job 339, Elberta,1965 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Job 340, Frankfort,1964-1965 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Job 341, Rogers City,1965 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Job 341, Rogers City, Blue – line Drawings,1964-1965 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Job 341, Rogers City, Specifications,1964 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Job 342, Frankfort,1965 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Job 343, Frankfort,1964-1965 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Job 344, Frankfort,1965-1966 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Job 344, Frankfort, Drawings,1965 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Job 345, Frankfort,1965 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Job 346, St. Ignace,1965 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Job 347, Frankfort, 1 of 2,1965 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Job 347, Frankfort, 2 of 2,1965 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Job 347, Frankfort, Contract and Estimates,1965 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Job 347, Frankfort, Drawings,1965 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Job 347, Frankfort, Indiana Limestone Correspondence,1965-1966 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Job 348, Elberta,1965 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Job 349, Mackinac Island,1965 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Job 350, Frankfort,1965 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Job 351, Frankfort,1966 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Job 352, Frankfort,1966 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Job 353, Frankfort,1966-1968 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Job 353, Frankfort,1969-1979 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Job 353, Frankfort, Drawings,1966-1969 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Job 353, Frankfort, Drawings,Undated (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Job 353, Frankfort, Preliminary Drawings and Calculations,1968 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Job 354, Traverse City,1966 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Job 354, Traverse City, Albert Kahn Associated Architects and Engineers Correspondence,1966 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Job 354, Traverse City, Blueprints,1966 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Job 354, Traverse City, Estimates,1966 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Job 354, Traverse City, Drawings,1966 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Job 355, Harbor Beach,1966 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Job 355, Harbor Beach, Contract and Estimate,1966 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Job 355, Harbor Beach, Hercules, Inc., Correspondence,1966 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Job 355, Harbor Beach, Indiana Limestone Company Freight Bill and Invoices,1966 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Job 355, Harbor Beach, Inspection and Progress Reports,1966 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Job 355, Harbor Beach, Plans and Specifications,1966 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Job 355, Harbor Beach, Photographs and Negatives,1966 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Job 356, Harbor Beach,1966 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Job 356, Harbor Beach, Plans,1966 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Job 356, Harbor Beach, Quotations and Estimates,1966 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Job 357, Frankfort,1966 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Job 358, New Buffalo,1966 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Job 358, New Buffalo, Clyde E. Williams and Associates,1965 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Job 358, New Buffalo, Contract and Bidding,1965 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Job 358, New Buffalo, Payment Estimates,1966 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Job 358, New Buffalo, Plans,1966 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Job 358, New Buffalo, Profiles,1966 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Job 359, Charlevoix,1967 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Job 359, Charlevoix, Drawings,1967 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Job 360, Two Creeks, WI,1967 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Job 262A, Frankfort,1967 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Job 363, Kewaunee, WI,1967 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Job 364, Frankfort,1968 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Job 365, Frankfort,1968 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 1 of 8,1968 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 2 of 8,1968 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 3 of 8,1968 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 4 of 8,1968 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 5 of 8,1968 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 6 of 8,1968 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 7 of 8,1968 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, 8 of 8,1968 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, Blue – line Drawings,1968 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Job 366, Charlevoix, Drawings,1968 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Job 367, Charlevoix,1968 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Job 368, Frankfort, 1 of 2,1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Job 368, Frankfort, 2 of 2,1968 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Job 368, Frankfort, Drawings,1968 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Job 369, Frankfort,1968 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Job 370, Frankfort,1969 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Job 371, Charlevoix,1969 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI,1969 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Contract and Bidding Papers,1969 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Divers Inspection Reports,1969 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Job Hours Breakdown,1969 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Orders,1969 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Pioneer Services Inc., 1 of 2,1969 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Pioneer Services Inc., 2 of 2,1969 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Plans,1969 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Pre – Construction Information,1969 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Pro Fab Drawings,1969 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Profiles,1969 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Progressive Fabrications,1969 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Shop Drawings,1969 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Job 372, Kewaunee, WI, Specifications,1969 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Job 373, Frankfort,1969 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Job 374, Burn’s Ditch, IN,1969 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Job 375, Charlevoix,1969 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Job 376, Traverse City,1969 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Job 376, Traverse City, Contract and Estimate,1969 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Job 376, Traverse City, Orders and Shop Drawings,1969 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Job 376, Traverse City, Plans and Specifications,1969 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Job 377, Charlevoix,1969 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Job 378, Detroit,1970 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Job 379, Ludington,1970 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Job 379, Ludington, Michigan Drilling,1970 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Job 380, Frankfort,1970 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Job 381, Frankfort,1970 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Job 382, Ludington, 1 of 2,1970 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Job 382, Ludington, 2 of 2,1970 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Job 382, Ludington,1971 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Job 382, Ludington, Bid and Contract,1970 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Job 382, Ludington, Blue – line Drawings,1970 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Job 382, Ludington, Estimates,1970 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Job 382, Ludington, Orders,1970-1971 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Job 382, Ludington, Progress and Job Hour Charts,1970-1971 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Job 383, Frankfort,1970 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Job 384, Traverse City,1970 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Job 385, Charlevoix,1970 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Job 386, Frankfort,1970 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Job 387, Bridgeman,1971 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Job 387, Bridgeman, Blue – line Drawings,1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Job 387, Bridgeman, Blueprints,1969 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Job 387, Bridgeman, Estimates,1970 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Job 387, Bridgeman, Job Summaries,1971-1972 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Job 387, Bridgeman, Profile Drawings,1971 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Job 387, Bridgeman, Specifications,1969 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, 1 of 2,1971 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, 2 of 2,1971 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, Armco Steel Correspondence,1971 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, Contract,1970 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, Drawing Index,1971 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, Drawings,1971 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, Newspaper Clippings,1971 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Job 388, Charlevoix, Photographs,1971 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Job 389, Cudahy, WI and Evanston, IL,1970 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Job 390, Frankfort,1970 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Job 391, Charlevoix,1970 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Job 392, Charlevoix,1970 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Job 393, Frankfort,1970 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Job 394, Frankfort,1970 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Job 395, Beaver Island,1971 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Job 395, Beaver Island, Contract,1971 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Job 395, Beaver Island, Drawings and Charts,1971 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Job 395, Beaver Island, Photographs,1971 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Job 396, Frankfort,1971 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Job 397, Frankfort,1971 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Job 398, Elberta,1971 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Job 399, Owosso,1971 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Job 400, Two Creeks, WI,1971 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Job 400, Two Creeks, WI, Blue – line Drawings,1971 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Job 400, Two Creeks, WI, Drawings,1971 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Job 401, Cudahy, WI,1971 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Job 402, Onekama,1971 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Job 403, Charlevoix,1971 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Job 404, Ludington,1971 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Job 405, Elberta,1971 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Job 406, Harbor Beach, 1 of 3,1971 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Job 406, Harbor Beach, 2 of 3,1971 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Job 406, Harbor Beach, 3 of 3,1971 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Job 406, Harbor Beach, Blue – line Drawings,1971 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Job 407, Charlevoix,1971 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Job 408, Ludington,1971 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 1 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 2 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 3 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 4 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 5 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 6 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 7 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 8 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 9 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 10 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 11 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Job 409, Ludington, 12 of 12,1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Job 409, Ludington, Articles,1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Job 409, Ludington, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 4,1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Job 409, Ludington, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 4,1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Job 409, Ludington, Blue – line Drawings, 3 of 4,1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Job 409, Ludington, Blue – line Drawings, 4 of 4,1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Job 409, Ludington, Drawings,1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Job 410, Frankfort,1971 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Job 411, Manistee,1971 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Job 411, Manistee, Drawings,1971 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Job 412, Manitowoc, WI,1971 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Job 413, Kewaunee, WI,1971 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Job 414, Harbor Beach,1971-1972 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Job 414, Harbor Beach, Blue – line Drawings,1971-1972 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Job 415, Frankfort,1971-1972 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Job 416, Frankfort,1971-1972 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Job 417, Charlevoix,1971 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Job 418, Frankfort,1972 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Job 419, Bridgman,1972 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Job 420, Bridgman,1972 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH,1972-1973 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH,1973-1980 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH, Bidding Papers,1972-1973 (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH, Contract,1972-1974 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH, Contract Performances,1973-1974 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH, Drawings,1972 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH, Drawings,1973-1974 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Job 421, Vermilion, OH, Orders,1973 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Job 422, Frankfort,1972 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Job 423, South Manitou Island,1972-1978 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Job 423, South Manitou Island, Drawings and Maps,1978 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, 1 of 2,1973 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, 2 of 2,1973 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Backfill Soundings,1974 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Contract,1973-1974 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Diver Inspection Reports, 1 of 3,1973 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Diver Inspection Reports, 2 of 3,1973 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Diver Inspection Reports, 3 of 3,1973 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Drawings, 1 of 2,1973 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Drawings, 2 of 2,1973 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Finkbeiner, Pettis and Strout Correspondence,1972-1974 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Orders,1973 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Job 424, Oak Harbor, OH, Photographs,1973 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Job 425, Frankfort,1973 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Job 426, Elberta,1973 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Job 427, Elberta,1973 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Job 428, Lake Township,1974 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Job 428, Lake Township, Consoer, Townsend and Associates Correspondence,1973-1974 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Job 428, Lake Township, Drawings,1973-1974 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Job 428, Lake Township, Price Brothers Correspondence,1973-1974 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Job 428, Lake Township, Proposal and Contract,1973 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Job 429, Kewaunee, WI,1973 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Job 430, Ludington,1973-1974 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Job 431, Harbor Beach,1973 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Job 432, Lorain, OH,1973-1975 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Job 432, Lorain, OH, Drawings,Undated (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Job 432, Lorain, OH, Photographs,1975 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Job 433, Lake Township,1974-1975 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Job 433, Lake Township, Contract, 1 of 2,1974 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Job 433, Lake Township, Contract, 2 of 2,1974 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Job 433, Lake Township, Price Brothers Correspondence,1974 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Job 434, Saugatuck,1974 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Job 434, Saugatuck, Bid and Contract,1974 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Job 434, Saugatuck, Blue – line Drawings,1974 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, 1 of 2,1974 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, 2 of 2,1974 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI,1975 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Blue –line Drawings, 1 of 2,1974 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Blue –line Drawings, 2 of 2,1974 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Contract Modifications and Progress Schedule,1974-1976 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Contract Modification #501 Correspondence,1974-1976 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Contract Performances,1974-1976 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Edward E. Gillen Company Correspondence,1974 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Edward E. Gillen Company Correspondence, 1 of 2,1975 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Edward E. Gillen Company Correspondence, 2 of 2,1975 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Estimate and Proposal,1974 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Specifications,1974 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Job 435, Kenosha, WI, Vulcan Materials Correspondence,1974-1976 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Job 436, Lorain, OH,1974 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Job 436, Lorain, OH, Blue – line Drawings,1974 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Job 437, Monroe,1974 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Job 438, Cleveland, OH,1974-1975 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Job 438, Cleveland, OH,1975-1976 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Job 438, Cleveland, OH, Bid, Proposal and Contract,1975 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Job 438, Cleveland, OH, Drawings,1974 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Job 438, Cleveland, OH, Original Claque Road Intake Plans, 1 of 2,1954 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Job 438, Cleveland, OH, Original Claque Road Intake Plans, 2 of 2,1954 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Job 439, Ludington,1975 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Job 440, Elberta,1974 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Job 441, Elberta,1975 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Job 442, Au Sable,1975 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Job 442, Au Sable, Contract, Estimate and Change of Orders,1975 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Job 442, Au Sable, Contract, Estimate and Change of Orders,1975 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Job 443, Ashtabula, OH,1975 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Job 444, Kenosha, WI,1974-1977 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Job 444, Kenosha, WI, Alvord, Burdict and Houston Correspondence,1975-1976 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Job 444, Kenosha, WI, Bid Proposal and Contract,1975 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Job 444, Kenosha, WI, Drawings,1975 (Box 151, Folder 6)